Achmad Syarif Hidayatullah

+6285161391514 | 🖂 achmadsyarif241@gmail.com | [in] linked.in/achmadsyarif | 👚 My Portfolio

One shot, give it your all

Summary

I am last-year undergraduate student of Business Administration major from Imam Muhammad bin Saud University who is always motivated to constantly develop my skill and grow professionally. I have strong interest in Front End Developer and also Software Developer. This ability has been proven on my experience as a Software Developer for a couple of year and also from some certificate I got, you can look up to my Linkedin. Despite I'm not an IT background, I will give the best I have and dedicate my skill on my works.

Work Experience

Software Developer | Bhumi Varta Technology | Tangerang (Remote) | June 2022 - Present

- Develop a dashboard for a festival held by the Indonesian Minister using ReactJS, Ant Design, SCSS, and ANTD Chart.
- Embrace teamwork with my team to develop and manage an app that has a thousand of users.
- Responsible to build map web app dashboard using dashboard.

Frontend Engineer (Part-Time) | Sagara Technology | Jakarta (Remote) | February 2022 – May 2022

- Develop an app for investing or funding using React.Js, NextJs, Ant Design and Material UI
- Worked closely with back-end team, UI/UX designers in implementing UI design to the website and integrate API to front-end to make web app more powerful.

Front-End Engineer Intern | Sagara Technology | Jakarta (Remote) | October 2021 – January 2022

- Develop website for social media using React. Js and Tailwind CSS
- Worked jointly with FE-team, BE-team, and also UI/UX designers to create impressive applications.
- Create a Mobile Responsive with CSS that allowed cross-platform accessibility to the website on any device with primary use on mobile

Education

Imam Muhammad bin Saud University | 2020 - present

Bachelor's Degree | Business Administration Semester 7 - Current GPA 4,71/5,00

Skills

Problem Solving

Attention to Detail

Fast Learner

Critical Thinking

Team Work

Strong Communication

Language

English

Arabic

Bootstrap / Tailwind

Indonesia

Programming Skills

Javascript / ES6

Python

SCSS/SASS

MongoDB

HTML5

GIT

React JS

JQuery

CSS3

Node JS